考特斯特工？我是邓杰
Agent Cortez? This is Danger D'Amo.
向我报告最新情况
Give me a status update.
视觉辨认已经完成
Visual ID has been made.
目标准时到达地点
The subject has entered the location right on time.
很好所有便衣特工请注意
Aces. All undercover agents, be on the alert.
目标“滴答人”偷走了航天科学局的迷你光碟
Subject known as Tick Tock has the stolen OSS mini disc.
1队和2队上前捉拿目标
Alpha and Bravo teams, move in to apprehend the target.
不许动
Freeze!
他有时间炸弹
He's got time bombs!
不能动的是你们
Be careful what you wish for!
“滴答人”带着航天科学局迷你光碟走了
Tick Tock has the stolen OSS mini disc and is on the move.
对不起我不能久留
Sorry I can't hang around.
我这就带3队去4分钟后到
I'm coming with a third team. On-site arrival in four minutes.
等不了4分钟我用滑索下去抓他更怏
We don't have four minutes! I'll get him faster with the zip line.
不赶快抓到他他会定住不知多少人
If I don't catch him now, who knows how many people he'll freeze?
你忘记了一个小细节
You forgot one tiny detail.
你怀孕了
You're pregnant.
医生说可以一直锻炼到临产
Yeah, well, they say you can exercise up until the last day of pregnancy,
就当是锻炼
so, here we go.
天啊
Oh, man! Ow!
- 怎么了 - 子宫收缩
- Whoa, what was that? - Contraction!
该放弃了你就要成为妈妈了
Time to hang it up. You're about to become a mom.
所以才要抓紧时间完成任务
All the more reason to get the job done now.
不能让“滴答人”再次跑掉
We can't let Tick Tock escape again.
呼吸
Breathe.
别撞到公交车
Try not to hit that bus.
- 屏蔽路上的噪音 - 屏蔽中
- Mute road noise. - Muting road noise.
- 呼叫威尔伯 - 呼叫中
- Call Wilbur. - Calling husband.
是你啊还好吗
Oh, there she is. How's my girl?
你刚下班？
You just leaving work?
对只是还有些小事
Yeah, just tying up a few things.
怀孕9个月的人还在不知疲倦的工作
Nine months pregnant and still working around the clock.
你恐怕是世界上最勤奋的室内设计师了
You've got to be the most dedicated interior decorator that ever lived.
我还能说什么我喜欢我的工作
What can I say? I love my work.
噢
Ooh!
我打电话是因为这件事
Here's what I really called about.
猜猜是谁要提前来了？
Guess who decided to pay us an early visit?
要生了？
Is this it?
我正在去医院的路上到那里见面？
I'm on my way to the hospital. Meet me there?
对医院别慌我这就去
Right. Hospital. Don't panic. I'm here for you.
你只需要
All you have to do…
平缓呼吸经常呼吸
…is breathe easy and breathe often…
慢慢来
…and take it nice and slow.
我非常爱你
I love you so… much.
保持呼吸
Keep breathing.
- 你不会有事的 - 知道了到医院见
- You're gonna be just fine. - Yep. Gotcha. See you there.
特工你就要生了等待后援吧
Agent, you're ready to pop. Wait for backup!
子宫收缩只相隔3分钟
Contractions are only three minutes apart.
我还有时间
I've got time.
好了滴答人把迷你光碟交出来
OK, Tick Tock. Hand over the mini disc.
- 这次不会 - 天
- Not this time. - Ah, man.
别低估她
Don't underestimate her.
好像我的羊水破了
I think my water just broke.
原来是别人尿裤子
I hope that was my water.
打败她
Clean her clock.
让着点我正子宫收缩呢
Cut me some slack, I'm having a contraction.
恭喜你
Congratulations…
我希望再有下次
I look forward to doing this again.
干得好考特斯特工
Swell work, Agent Cortez.
漂亮我就知道你能行
Aces. I knew you had it in you.
如果光碟到了坏人手中
If this got into the wrong hands,
世界将会停止运转
our world would've stopped in its tracks.
好像是航天科学局的资料片
Looks like an old OSS file.
末日计划终极武器
Project Armageddon, the ultimate weapon.
这种武器不光能消灭敌人也能消灭所有人
This baby not only takes out your enemy, it takes out everyone.
只有时间没了人们才能注意到时间
No one ever notices time until it's gone.
这是我们的协议
This was our agreement.
最后一次任务之后我就永远退出
One last mission and I'm out for good.
你真的要辞职？抛下我们不管了？
You're really gonna take a powder on us? Leave us high and dry?
再也不能吊在滑索上或者汽车追逐了
No more dangling from zip lines or high-speed chases.
我的家人现在需要我
My family needs me now.
不能让他们知道我是间谍
And they can never know I was a spy.
我尊重这一点但是给你一条建议：告诉他们你的身份
I respect that, agent. But a word of advice: tell 'em who you are.
人生短暂不要有那么多秘密
Life's too short for secrets.
为我们生一个神通广大的孩子好吗
Push out a good one, a nice little fire-breather for us, all right?
航天科学局的未来全系于此
The future of the OSS depends on it.
不要干站着嚼口香糖了
Let's not stand around bumping gums, people.
我想弄明白是什么让滴答人滴答
I wanna figure out what makes Tick Tock tick.
拇指搏斗
Thumb battle.
开始
Go.
孩子们我想到一个新的真人秀节目
Hey, kids. I got a new idea for a reality show.
名叫威尔伯：间谍猎手
It's called Wilbur Wilson: Spy Hunter,
在电视上追捕真正的间谍
where I hunt real spies on TV.
- 你们觉得怎么样 - 挺不错的爸爸
- What do you think? - Uh, it's pretty out there, Dad.
- 打败你了 - 漂亮的击倒
- Got you. - Nice takedown.
我赢了一次你去哪里找间谍呢
one point for me. Yeah, I mean, where are you gonna find a spy?
- 嗨老公 - 嗨亲爱的
- Hi! Honey! - Hey, sweetheart!
你真美
Hey, you look great.
你输给我一块钱
You owe me a dollar.
我就知道能比她来的更早
Told you we would get here before her.
我说过不着急但是我们等了一个晚上
I said take it slow, but that was a night shy of eternity.
和一个早上
and a morning past forever.
继母干什么事都迟到
Stepmother is always late for everything.
严格来说我是来早了因为预产期本来是明天
Technically I'm early, 'cause the baby wasn't even due until tomorrow.
放松
Ease up.
怎么现在才来
What took so long?
呃只是忘了时间
Uh, just must have lost track of time.
- 天啊 - 好了
- Oh, God! - Here we go! Oh!
天你们看你们看
Jeez! Guys, guys, guys, guys.
从现在起一切都将变得不同
From this point on, everything'll be different.
好的不同吧
In a good way, right?
是的你会有一个妹妹
Yeah. And you'll have a new baby sister…
倒计时5 4 3 2…
in five, four, three, two…
《非常小特务4：时间大盗》
我每次寻找
I put my life on the line.
我们身边的间谍
every time I search for…
都是冒着生命危险
…the spies among us.
看
Look!
我是威尔伯
I'm Wilbur Wilson…
间谍猎手
… Spy Hunter.
每周一晚黄金时间
Mondays after your local news.
最后一片熏肉
Last piece of bacon.
我的
Mine!
你的
Yours.
宝宝又甩食物了？
Is the baby throwing food again?
应该是的
I would say so.
你们照看一下她
Can you watch her, please?
我要去再换换衣服
I have to go change again.
再一次
Again.
干什么啊
Ah! Seriously?
她的屁能把家里的油漆熏得脱落下来
Her gas bombs are gonna take the paint right off this house.
- 你照看她 - 不 你
- You watch her. - No. You.
- 来场憋气大赛？- 来就来
- Breath-holding contest? - You're on.
我赢了一次
one point for me.
- 早上好小间谍猎手 - 爸爸
- Good morning, little Spy Hunters. - Dad!
你有时间和我们一起吃早餐吗
Do you have time to eat breakfast with us?
- 当然有 - 好啊
- I sure do. - Yes!
不我没有
No, I don't.
我发誓就在刚才
I swear I had an extra five minutes…
我还有5分钟的时间
…just a few minutes ago.
- 时间去哪儿了 - 我说过他不会有时间
- Where'd the time go? - Told you he wouldn't have time.
你输给我一块钱
You owe me a dollar.
你记得我们的五年计划吗
Hey… Do you remember our five-year plan?
如果我的节目顺利
If my show does well,
那么我就会有无数的时间
then I'll have all the time in the world.
来陪着你和你
to spend with you and you, OK?
同时时间却在溜走
Meanwhile, time is just slipping away.
- 早上好老公 - 再见老婆
- Morning, honey. - Oh, bye, honey.
- 我要去上班了 - 呃好
- I gotta get to work. - Oh, um, OK.
- 送别拥抱？- 好
- Uh, good-bye hug? - Oh, yeah.
呃
Uh…
- 再见 - 再见
- Bye. - Bye.
- 丽贝卡在学校要乖知道吗 - 我知道
- Rebecca, behave at school. OK? - I know.
- 塞西尔… - 呃
- And, Cecil. - Uh…
要喂狗
…feed the dog.
它并不吃饭
He doesn't really eat.
只是看着我们
He just watches us.
给阿格诺
Here, Argonaut.
挺古怪的
It's kind of creepy.
我们最担心的事发生了时间加速了
our worst fear has happened: Time is speeding up.
你们不是吓唬我的吧这是真的？
You're not cranking my chain, are you? This is on the up and up?
- 晚上好先生 - 晚上好？
- Good night, sir. - Good night?
胡说什么美女你刚吃完午饭回来
What are you talking about, doll face? You just got back from lunch.
- 可现在是五点 - 五点？
- But it's five o'clock, sir. - Five o'clock?
末日装置
The Armageddon device.
我们时间不多了
We're running out of time.
他拿花生果酱三明治蒙住你的脸
So he put a peanut butter and jelly sandwich in your face.
然后偷走了你的作业？
and then he stole your homework?
严格来说是他的作业我只是替他做
Technically, it was his homework. I was just doing it for him.
你呢丽贝卡今天过得怎么样
And what about you, Miss Rebecca? How was your day?
和以往一样
Same old, same old.
我听说了
So I heard.
校长打电话给我说起你的恶作剧
The principal called me about your pranks.
- 孩子们 - 爸爸坐在我身边
- Hey, kids! - Dad! Come, sit by me!
对不起孩子们我要先把报告写完才能去干别的事
Sorry, kids, but I have to go write up this report before I can do anything.
给我留点剩饭
Save me some leftovers.
喂爸爸你能教我怎么做间谍猎手吗
Hey, Dad? Can you teach me how to be a Spy Hunter?
这种事总是有时间的
Well, there's always time for that.
好跟着我重复
OK. Repeat after me:
我是西塞尔间谍猎手
"I'm Cecil Wilson, Spy Hunter,
我等会就抓住你
and I'll catch you… later."
我是西塞尔间谍猎手
I'm Cecil Wilson, Spy Hunter,
我等会就抓住你
and I'll catch you… later!
重要的是
Here's the important part.
扬起眉毛
Lift the eyebrow.
尊重金拱门
Respect the golden arch.
这是我的秘诀
That's my secret.
你抓住多少间谍了
How many spies have you caught?
呃…一个也没有
Um… Well, none.
不过这不是节目的目的
Um… But that's not really what the show's about.
这么说你不是抓间谍的超级英雄？
So you're not a spy-catching superhero?
目前还不是
No, not yet…
不过…
…but…
小宝宝怎么样
How's my girl?
她今天大便两次
She made two poopies today.
两次？离我的记录只差6次了
Two poopies? She's six away from the house record.
噢
Oh!
不要流鼻涕
Now, don't get snotty.
我没有食欲了
I lost my appetite.
我去和她谈谈
I'll go talk to her.
我做错什么了？
What am I doing wrong?
我尽力和她交流
I've tried so hard to connect with her.
- 可她就是恨我 - 她不恨你
- But she just hates me. - No, she doesn't hate you.
- 他绝对恨我 - 不是的也许有一点点
- She totally hates me. - No, she doesn't. Maybe a little.
我开玩笑的
I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
她只是还没有适应家里的变化
I think she's just trying to adjust to a new situation.
我们结婚都两年了
We've been married for two years.
对
Right.
自从有了继母
Dad's had less time for us.
爸爸陪我们的时间就少了
ever since Stepmother entered the picture.
她还有事瞒着我们
And she's keeping something from us.
我能感觉到她有秘密身份
I can feel it. She's not who she says she is!
你觉得她不是室内设计师？
You don't think she's really an interior decorator?
你看看家里的的装饰她显然是个坏人
Well, look at this place! She's obviously evil.
我觉得她挺好
Well, I think she's nice.
她有事瞒着我们
There is something she's hiding from us.
那也不能对她用蓝色奶酪炸弹啊
Doesn't mean she deserves your blue cheese dressing bomb.
我最好的恶作剧
My best prank yet.
我的听觉不行使我别的感觉敏锐
Not hearing very well increased my other senses.
比如嗅觉
Like smell.
放心反正她从来不进我的房间
Don't worry, she never comes into my room anyway.
你有时间吗
Do you have a sec?
有
Yes.
我在地下室里
I was going through the basement.
找到一样东西你可能想要
and I found some things that I thought you might wanna have.
妈妈
Mom.
我知道你想她我永远替代不了她
I know you miss your mom and I could never replace her.
只要我们能做朋友我会很高兴的
I just would really like it if maybe we could be friends?
妈妈经常说她喜欢我的恶作剧
Mom always said she loved my practical jokes.
我喜欢你的恶作剧我觉得你十分有趣
I love your practical jokes. I think you're hilarious.
你觉得我有趣？
You think I'm funny?
你上个月捉弄你爸爸
The one you did last month to your father.
把蓝莓浆掺进牙膏里
when you filled his toothpaste with blueberry filling?
他的牙齿蓝了四天
And his teeth were blue for like four days.
太厉害了
That was epic.
还有那次我把他的鼻子剃须刀
And how about the time I hooked up his nose hair clipper.
连到电锯上
to a power saw?
我的杰作之一
Some of my best work.
还有把婴儿爽身粉放进吹风机里
Or the baby powder in the hair dryer trick?
那本来是捉弄你的
I had meant that prank for you.
我知道
I know.
对不起
I'm sorry.
没关系只是个玩笑
It's OK. It was just a joke.
有件东西
There's something, um…
我想送给你
…I would like you to have.
这是我像你这么大的时候我父母送给我的
This is something my parents gave me when I was around your age.
我妈妈说它会永远保护我
And my mother said it would always protect me,
即便是在最黑暗的时刻
even in my darkest hour.
我觉得她的意思是
What I think she meant by that was,
我会永远的到她的爱和支持
I would always have her love and support.
你真要送给我？
You're really giving this to me?
它对我和我的家庭来说很特殊
It's something that's very special to me and my family.
我想送给你
and I want you to have it…
因为你是如此特殊
…because you're so very special.
丽贝卡
Rebecca…
我很期待我们成为朋友
…I'm really looking forward to us being friends.
我也是
Me, too.
晚安
Good night.
玛丽萨等等
Marissa, wait!
我…
I'm so…
真对不起
…sorry.
干得不错
Good going.
我想告她的
I tried to warn her!
你需要和她和解
You got to make it up to her.
为什么老是我道歉
Why do I have to be the one to always apologize?
比如那次你一直说话…
Like what about that time that you just kept on talking and I was…
我关闭了我的助听器
I turned off my hearing aids.
好吧我和她和解
OK! I'll make it up to her!
他说得对
He's right, you know.
节目的名字叫做“间谍猎手”
I mean, the show is called Spy Hunter.
我总要捉住一个间谍才行
At some point, I should actually catch a spy.
他觉得我很没用
He thinks I'm a complete loser.
他不是这个意思
That's not what he meant.
他们只想能多点时间和你在一起
They just wanna spend more time with you.
什么气味
What is that smell?
宝宝又吐在你身上了？
Oh, did the baby spit up on you again?
- 重要新闻… - 差不多吧
- In breaking news… - Something like that.
我们最担心的情况得到了证实
…our worst fears have been confirmed.
据科学家所说每天的时间更少了
According to scientists, there are now, literally, less hours in the day.
研究表明时间在消失
Studies show that time is running out.
时间在加速
Time is speeding up.
开始我们失去的只是一瞬可现在我们正失去几个小时
At first, we were losing nanoseconds, but now we 're losing hours.
到明天我们会失去几天到后天我们会失去一年
By tomorrow, we'll have lost days. By the day after that, a year.
以这个速度我们很快就没有时间了
At this rate, we will be completely out of time… in no time.
专家对引起这一现象的原因莫衷一是
Experts are divided on what's causing this phenomenon,
不过有一个人宣称对此事负责这是我们刚刚收到的录像
although one man has claimed credit. We received this video moments ago.
世界公民们
Citizens of the world,
我判决你们全部犯有浪费时间的罪名
I find you all guilty of wasting time.
时间都花在无谓的追求上
You fill your days with meaningless pursuits.
而不是珍惜和你爱的人在一起的时光
instead of treasuring moments with those you love.
时间不再是你们轻易得到的
You will no longer take time for granted,
我要剥夺你们所有的时间
for I am taking all of the time in the world from you.
末日计划已经启动
Project Armageddon has been activated.
我会继续加快时间直到耗尽
and I will continue to speed up time until time runs out,
世界将会结束
and the world will end.
我是时间守护者
I am the Time Keeper.
我想要更多的时间
and I want more time!
几分钟前航天科学局局长邓杰对此发表评论
Only minutes ago, OSS Director Danger D'Amo addressed the threat.
航天科学局将会找到这个时间守护者等找到了他
The OSS will find this Time Keeper, and when we do,
我们会打烂他的时钟
we will punch his clock.
现在每小时减少一分钟
There's a decrease of one minute per hour as now…
滴答人逃走了
Tick Tock has escaped.
大事不妙
Oh, this is not good.
其实这是大好事
Actually, this is awesome.
如果我能采访这个时间持有者
Could you imagine the promotion I would get.
我会得到多大的升职啊
if I landed an interview with this guy, the Time Holder?
- 时间守护者 - 而且抓住国际大坏蛋
- Time Keeper. - Not to mention the hero factor.
我的英雄形象就建立起来了我喜欢
for tracking down an international supervillain. Not too shabby.
老公我觉得孩子们现在需要的不是你做英雄
Honey, I think being a hero isn't really what the kids need from you right now.
这正是他们现在需要的
It's just what they need now.
是世界需要的
It's what the world needs.
你对我承诺的时间宝石呢
Where is the Chronos Sapphire you promised me?
时间不等人但会等我
Time waits for no man, no man but me.
那颗宝石是唯一可以
That one little rock is the only element.
阻止末日装置的东西
that can stop the Armageddon device.
相信我会到我们手上的
Trust me, it will be ours.
时间和我的耐心都不多了
Time and my temper are short.
你如果浪费我的时间
You waste my time…
我就杀了你
…and I'll waste you.
我们会找到宝石
We will find the Chronos Sapphire…
等我们找到
…and when we do…
没人能阻止我们
…no one will be able to stop us.
没人
No one.
好宝贝女儿你困了吧
OK, princess. You're a little sleepy head, huh?
哦不
Oh, no.
航天科学局指示：只能你看到
OSS directive. For your eyes only.
时间守护者的威胁被确认
Time Keeper threat confirmed.
需要时间宝石来阻止末日装置
Chronos Sapphire needed to stop Armageddon.
马上把时间宝石送到航天科学局
Deliver Chronos to OSS immediately.
哦丽贝卡
Oh, Rebecca.
希望你在研究怎么道歉
I hope you're working on that apology.
还要注明一句：这不关西塞尔的事
Make sure you write "P.S., Cecil is innocent."
手工做的优惠券
A handmade coupon,
可以一个月不用做家务活
good for one free month of all household chores.
以及一个月内不发生恶作剧
And no pranks for a whole month.
以及一周内不发生恶作剧
"And no pranks for a week."
喂丽贝卡
Hey, Rebecca?
昨晚的项链还在吗
Do you have that necklace from last night?
在怎么了
Yeah. Why?
我想问问我能不能…
I was just wondering if maybe I could, um…
要回来？
…maybe I can have it back?
你想要回项链？
You want the necklace back?
我想清洗一下因为很旧了
I realized it needs to be cleaned, and, uh… you know, it's old.
我明白了交给我你不放心
Oh, I get it. You can't trust me with it.
你不是说这项链很特殊我也很特殊吗
What happened to "This necklace is so special, and so are you"?
原来这不是你的真心话
Am I supposed to pretend that you really meant that?
我需要要回项链现在无法解释
I just need the necklace back. I can't really explain it right now.
给你吧
You can have it!
反正我不稀罕你的破项链
I never wanted your stupid necklace anyway.
你只关心自己从来不关心我们
You only care about yourself! You don't care about us at all!
我有一个重要任务不事情
I have to go on an important mission, I mean, errand.
冰箱里有点心
There are snacks in the fridge.
我1 0分钟后回来
I'll be back in ten minutes.
你们需要什么吗
Do you guys need anything?
我妈妈
My mom.
我们不用
We'll be fine.
好
Right.
阿格诺
Argonaut.
看着孩子们
Watch the kids.
房子武装完毕
House is now armed.
系好安全带宝宝
Buckle up, baby.
- 宝宝安全 - 好
- Baby secure. - All right.
我们开车走吧
Let's go for a ride.
喂你不是还给玛丽莎了吗
Hey! I thought you gave that back to Marissa.
等着她看到盒子里吧
Wait till she looks in the box.
欢迎回来特工
Welcome back, agent.
这是时间宝石吗没有它我们就完了
Is that the Chronos Sapphire? Without that, our goose is cooked.
给妈妈谢谢宝贝
Give it to Mommy. Thank you, pumpkin.
来给我吧
Here, give it to me.
噢
Oh.
又一出恶作剧
Another prank.
- 宝宝的饭 - 对不起
- Baby food. - I'm sorry.
我的女儿心情不太好
My stepdaughter is a little… upset.
项链在她那里
She has the necklace.
- 我去要回来 - 时间宝石可以等等
- I can get it back. - Chronos Sapphire can wait.
你的老对手滴答人逃走了
Your old pallie Tick Tock has just been made.
你是唯一能抓住他的人
and you're the only one that can scoop him up.
你又回来工作了
Pop the clutch. You're back on the clock.
不管时间宝石了吗
What about the Chronos?
你抓住滴答人就能找到时间守护者
You nab Tick Tock, he'll lead us to the Time Keeper.
不需要时间宝石
We don't need the Chronos.
那么丽贝卡可以留着项链
So Rebecca can keep the necklace.
那对她是个很大的安慰
It would mean a lot if she could.
好我干我要先去找到孩子
OK. I'll do it. I just have to go get my kids first.
那些小家伙不会有事的
Those ankle biters'll be fine!
我是1 7号探索者我们锁定了时间宝石的位置
This is Seeker 17. We have a lock on the Chronos Sapphire.
重复我们找到了时间宝石
Repeat, we have found the Chronos Sapphire.
准备破门而入
Prepare to breach the entrance.
你不该这么做的
You really shouldn't do that.
如果你一定要干让她长上吸血鬼的牙
But if you're going to, give her vampire teeth.
警告家里即将遭到攻击
Warning, residence subject to immediate attack.
立刻到恐慌房间躲避
Please take shelter in the panic room now.
你的恶作剧水平越来越高了
You're really stepping up your game with these pranks.
这不是我的恶作剧
That's not my prank.
警告家里即将遭到攻击
Warning, residence subject to immediate attack.
立刻到恐慌房间躲避
Take shelter in the panic room now.
- 恐慌房间在哪儿 - 别上当
- Where's the panic room? - Don't fall for it.
这显然是玛丽萨在讨好我
This is obviously Marissa's attempt to get me back.
立刻到恐慌房间躲避
Take shelter in the panic room now.
如果不去的话难道还能
Oh, and if we don't, I suppose something really terrible.
发生可怕的事吗
will happen to us.
扫描中
Scanning.
身份确认请立刻进入恐慌房间
Identity match. Please enter the panic room now.
- 立刻进入恐慌房间 - 走吧丽贝卡
- Enter the panic room now. - Let's go, Rebecca.
立刻进入恐慌房间
Enter the panic room now.
这里显然就是恐慌房间
Well, this is obviously the panic room.
- 为什么 - 因为这是个房间我又在恐慌
- Why? - 'Cause it's a room, and I'm panicking.
你们好孩子们
Hello, children.
我嫁给你们父亲的时候设置了这个恐慌房间
I had this panic room installed when I married your father.
以备我的工作使得家人受到威胁
in the event that my work ever put the family in danger.
她的工作？
Her work?
有件事我从未告诉你们
There's something I never told you about myself.
因为这关系到国家安全
because it was a matter of national security.
我是个间谍
I am a spy.
我们的继母是间谍？
our stepmother's a spy?
不可能
Impossible.
她没那个派头
She's not cool enough.
阿格诺是先进的守护者机器人
Argonaut is an Advanced Robotic Guardian Operative.
用于守护你们
designed to protect you.
我仍然觉得这是个恶作剧
I still think this is a prank.
这不是恶作剧
This is not a prank.
狗在说话
The dog is talking.
我注意到了
I noticed.
这不是你们想看到的吧
Well, it's not the sort of thing you'd miss, is it, really?
一个漂亮的小狗用英国口音说话就像007
A small, handsome dog talking with an English accent, like James Bond.
总之我的任务是保护你们来击个掌
Anyway, I've been assigned to protect you, so give me five.
这是很酷的做法吧握握手也行
That's what cool people say, isn't it? Anyway, let's shake hands.
你好你好
Hello. How do you do?
不我不喜欢这样需要你还给我
Ah! Oh, no! I hate when that happens! I am gonna need that back.
哨兵模式？攻击模式？
Sentry mode? Attack mode?
还是保持在哨兵模式吧
I think you better keep it in sentry mode.
放回去越快越好
Pop it back on, any time you're ready.
- 有道理 - 说真的
- Good thinking. - No, seriously.
放回去吧我要摔倒了
Can I have it back now? 'Cause I am gonna fall over.
恐慌房间受到攻击
The panic room is being attacked.
你们必须离开
You must leave now.
喷气式雪橇将会带你们到航天科学局总部
The jet luges will take you to OSS headquarters.
坐下搞笑吧
And sit. Do you get it?
一般是人让狗坐下
It's what humans usually say to dogs.
我颠倒过来了
I reversed it, I flipped it.
这一路会很愉快的
Oh, this is gonna be great.
告诉你们我们将会…
I tell you, we're gonna have a…
我一般吃了草或者拖鞋才会这么反胃
I usually have to eat grass or a slipper to feel this sick. Oh.
我只是还没适应过来没事没事
I wasn't ready, that's all. I'm fine, I'm fine.
不要让时间宝石跑掉
Do not let the Chronos Sapphire get away!
微型摄像头也没什么稀奇了
A mini camera is not that impressive anymore.
有的人骨头上都有
People have them in their phones.
有多少
Well, how small is it?
- 不可能 - 爸爸
- That's impossible. - Dad!
- 对不起 - 什么
- Sorry. - What?
爸爸帮帮我们
Dad, help us!
对不起我身后有飞行表演
Sorry, there was an air show behind me.
不可能存在隐形粉末
There's no such thing as invisibility powder.
好阿格诺说话吧
All right, Argonaut. Start talking.
那些戴着护目镜的人是谁为什么来这里
Who were those guys with the giant goggles? What do they want?
玛丽萨做间谍多长时间了
How long has Marissa been a spy?
你们继母完成任务之后会回答你们的全部问题
OK. Your stepmom will answer all of your questions post-mission.
我有个问题谁在驾驶这种飞机
I have a question. Who's flying this thing?
不是你吗
I thought you were.
糟糕他们好像来者不善
Oh, no. They do not look like pet lovers.
孩子们好看到这个说明你们的喷气飞机正受到攻击
Hello, children. If you're watching this, your escape jets are under attack.
必须采用躲避动作
We are going to have to initiate evasive maneuvers.
让你们更快到达航天科学局总部
to get you to OSS even faster.
- 坐稳了 - 惨了
- Brace yourselves. - Oh, great.
就像电子游戏
It's like a big video game.
握住控制杆稳稳地驾驶
Grab your controller and steer slowly!
- 哇 - 我要坠机了
- Whoa! - I'm gonna crash!
我想吐
I'm gonna hurl.
吐在袋子里不要沾到我的毛上
Right. Puke goes in the bag, not on my fur.
他们靠近了
They're gaining!
塞西尔
Cecil!
做点什么
Do something!
他在做在呕吐
He is doing something. He's puking.
还需要一个袋子
We might need a bigger bag.
也需要一个飞船
In fact, we might need a bigger spaceship.
这里难闻死了不能开开窗吗
It smells like fish socks in here. Can we at least open a window?
里面不好玩
Ugh. It's not much fun in here.
喂你也打开了我的窗户
Hey! You opened up mine!
新鲜空气有帮助
Fresh air. That helps.
我喜欢我喜欢把头伸出窗外我最喜欢的事
I love this. I love sticking my head out the window. It's my favorite thing.
对不起
Sorry!
塞西尔你还有几个呕吐袋？
Cecil! How may puke bags do you have left?
利用好了
Make 'em count!
好样的西塞尔
Good job, Cecil!
永远不要低估呕吐的力量
Never underestimate the power of puke.
阿格诺特工报告
Agent Argonaut reporting.
听着 孩子们都没事
Listen, the kids are fine.
但是房子就不一定了
I can't say the same about the house.
孩子们干了什么坏事
Why? What did they do?
不是他们干的是滴答人的手下毁了房子
They didn't do anything. They didn't destroy the house. Tick Tock's men did.
什么阿格诺不是让你看着他们吗
What?! Argonaut, I told you to watch them!
我看着他们的看着他们呕吐惊叫
I am watching them. I'm watching them puke and scream.
- 你要给我额外补贴 - 把他们带到航天局
- We've gotta discuss hazard pay. - Just get them to the OSS.
我要加薪
I want a raise!
希望有个人能去接他们
There's only one person I want waiting there to greet them.
航天局总部你要联系谁
OSS Headquarters. How can I direct your call?
我救了你的命赢了你一次
I saved your life. one point for me.
随你便吧呕吐袋炸弹是我的点子
Whatever. The puke bags were my idea.
你们怎么老是争吵你们是姐弟
Why do you argue about everything? You're brother and sister.
就像猫和狗整天打架
You're fighting like cats and dogs,
狗和猫打架我能理解
which I could understand why cats and dogs fight.
因为猫很讨厌你们要淡定
Cats are awful. Just chillax.
这是我自创的一个时髦的词
Part "chill, " part "relax." I fused 'em to make a trendy word.
欢迎来到航天局
Welcome to the OSS.
你是谁
Who are you?
卡门航天局特工
Carmen Cortez, secret agent of the OSS.
你们继母是我姑姑
Your stepmom is my aunt.
警告：世上有个大坏蛋
So, a word of caution to you would-be supervillains out there…
最好的应对武器就是…果酱面包
Your best defense may be… a jelly donut.
我胡说什么啊难道还能
What am I saying? What are they gonna do with that?
用果酱面包砸敌人吗
What, are they gonna throw them at 'em?
说吧我太帅了
Just say it. I'm too attractive.
应该承认
Let's face it.
我从没抓过间谍也永远不会
I've never caught a spy, and I probably never will.
我建议我们追捕时间守护者
I say we go after the Time Keeper.
这不现实
Oh, that's realistic.
间谍节目做得怎么样了
Where are you at with that piece for Spy Week?
要到周五呢
It's not due till Friday.
今天就是周五
It is Friday.
时间加速了威尔森没看新闻吗
Time's speeding up, Wilson. Don't you keep up with the news?
给我随便拍点素材
Get me something on someone, anyone!
昨天就交给我
And get it to me yesterday.
否则你明天就不用来电视台上班了知道吗
or there won't be a tomorrow for you at the station. Got it?
到了应该严肃的时候了
It's time to get serious.
玛丽萨不接电话也许她设置了无线电沉默
Marissa's not picking up. Maybe she's under radio silence.
有很多事要让她解释
She's got a lot of explaining to do, man.
她没说过是个间谍？
She never told you she was a spy, huh?
不过她已经退役了
Well, in her defense, she was retired.
- 你好 - 嗨 阿格诺
- Well, hello. - Hey, Argonaut!
你长这么高了这是钛合金吗
You're a big girl now. Is that titanium alloy?
- 想吃吗 - 请给我
- Treat? - Yes, please.
谢谢
Cheers.
酷
Cool.
想看看我开始做间谍的地方吗
Wanna see how I got started as a spy?
想
Yeah!
这是以前的小特务部门
This is the old Spy Kids division.
哇
Woa.
因为经费削减7年前关闭了
They shut it down seven years ago due to budget cuts.
很遗憾当时是领先时代的
Really sad. It was ahead of its time.
小特务部门是航天局的精英少年部门
Spy Kids were an elite juvenile division of the OSS.
我要让你爆炸
I'm going to explode you.
用于去成年间谍去不了的地方
Established to go where adult spies couldn't go.
做普通间谍做不了的事
and do what ordinary spies couldn't do.
拉菲是我啊我们一起上的学
Ralphie, it's me! We went to the academy together.
你好吗…
How you do…
明白了它被关闭了也好它挺烦人的
Oh. Now I see what, they've turned him off. Just as well. He's annoying.
我希望将来能重启小特工部门
I'd like to bring back the Spy Kids division one day.
我们称之为大皮靴和锤子手
We call those Stompers and Hammer Hands.
利用电子场产生超人的力量
They use electron fields to create superhuman impact force.
太棒了
These are awesome.
你能捏碎东西
You can crush things.
野外伏击必用品
"Field ambush supplies"?
用于帮助间谍在现场设置陷阱
Built to help a spy create on-the-spot booby traps.
埋伏，混乱还有恶作剧
ambushes, mass confusion, and pranks.
- 恶作剧？- 这样吧
- Pranks? - I'll tell you what.
我允许你们每人挑选一样东西作为纪念品
I'll let you guys pick out one gadget each as a souvenir.
- 我的 - 我的
- Mine. - Mine.
别太激动了我只是让你们选择
Don't get too excited. I said that I'd let you guys pick out a gadget,
但没说过会启动它
but I didn't say I'd activate it.
在当年最出色的小间谍
Back in the day, the kids who made the best spies.
不会等着设计出最棒的器械
were the ones who didn't wait around for the perfect gadgets.
而是用已有的东西来完成任务
They made stuff happen with what they had on hand.
这是谁
Who's that?
我和我弟弟朱尼
Me and my brother, Juni.
我们是小间谍计划的第一个和最后一个人
We were the first and last of the Spy Kids program.
他现在在哪儿
Where is he?
我们不该谈起他我们走
We shall not speak of him. Let's go.
这就是我们参观的终点
And this is where our grand tour ends.
在这儿等着玛丽萨很快就来接你们
Wait here. Marissa will pick you guys up in a minute.
我们能成为小间谍计划的候选人吗
Can we be candidates for the new Spy Kids program?
时间证明一切对不起我该走了
Time will tell. Sorry, guys, gotta go.
航天局给了我们很多任务
OSS has us working around the clock.
我们必须阻止时间守护者趁时间守护者还没有阻止时间
We have to stop the Time Keeper before the Time Keeper stops time.
时间守护者不像是坏人的名字吧
The Time Keeper. That's not much of a villain's name, is it?
时间守护者他有手表吧
Oh, the Time Keeper. Has he got a watch, has he?
这名字一点不吓人
It's not a scary name at all.
垃圾
Rubbish.
你已到达本次任务目的地
You have reached your destination for this mission.
祝你好运特工
Good luck, agent.
滴答人攻击了我们的房子
So Tick Tock attacked our house.
追逐你的哥哥姐姐
and chased after your brother and sister.
你看我们应该做什么
What do you think we should do?
消灭
Annihilate.
消灭？好主意
Annihilate? Good thinking.
欢迎回到快乐时光特工穿上套装
Welcome back to the big-time, agent. Suit up.
情报显示滴答人在这里
Intel places Tick Tock at this location.
找到他让他引着我们找到时间守护者的末日装置
Spot him and let him lead us to the Time Keeper's Armageddon device.
然后汇报等待后援
Then call in and wait for backup.
这就是我的后援
Here's my backup.
你我需要你六点到这里
All right, you. I need you at six o'clock, right here.
快点快点
Come on! Bring it in.
末日装置随时都会到
The Armageddon device will be here any minute.
我们必须为它的到来做好准备
and we must be ready for its arrival!
掩护出口
Uh, cover the exit.
好好样的
There you go. Good work.
集中精力集中精力
Focus up, focus. Focus!
你干什么还有很短的时间了
What are you doing? We're moments away.
我的计划就要完成了
My plan is almost complete.
只需要从烦人的孩子那里得到时间宝石
I just need to get the Chronos back from those meddlesome kids.
嘘
Shh…
搞什么刚才是你吗
Oh! Are you kidding me? Is that you?
你的传送器掉了？
Did you drop your transmission?
天啊你们别放屁
Oh, my God. Gentlemen, please.
这个屁难闻死了
That smells like lentils and desperation.
天真是的跟着人跑
My God, that's mental. It's following you.
回到位置上专心听
Get back on your marks. Focus.
熏得我都看不见了
I'm blinded. Ow!
它来了终于来了
It's here, it's here. It's finally here.
各就各位这是我们都在等待的时刻
Places, everyone. This is the moment we've all been waiting for.
来的正准时
Right on time.
滴滴答滴滴答
Hickory-dickory dock.
间谍跑到钟表上
The spy ran up the clock.
时钟敲打了一下间谍就完了
The clock struck one, and the spy was done.
滴答人胜利了
Game, set, and match, Tick Tock.
慢着
Wait a minute. Hold on.
这就是你的助手？一个挖鼻孔的宝宝？
This is your sidekick? A nose-picking baby?
各位进来
Gentlemen, get in here.
宝宝看来我们中了圈套
Baby, looks like we've been set up.
消灭她
Finish her. Boom.
嘣
Boom.
祝你下次好运
Better luck next time!
罪行越大就会越开心
The bigger the crime, the better the time!
他真让我恼火
He is really starting to tick me off.
10个绿瓶子挂在墙上
"Ten green bottles hanging on a wall.
如果一个不小心掉下来…
"And if one green bottle should accidentally fall."
我还在生继母的气
I'm still mad at Stepmother…
玛丽莎
Marissa.
竟然不告诉我们她是间谍
…for not telling us she was a spy.
也没告诉爸爸
For not telling Dad.
也许她辞职是为了能有时间陪我们
Maybe she quit to make more time for us.
得了吧
Yeah, right.
你不是也想当间谍吗
Well, wouldn't you wanna be a spy?
我会的
I will be.
比玛丽莎更强的间谍
Even better spy than Marissa.
你去干什么
What are you up to?
卡门说了优秀的小间谍不会干等着
Carmen said that the best Spy Kids were the ones who didn't wait around.
他们主动把事情做成
They went out and made stuff happen.
必须是很出色的事情
It would have to be something really amazing.
- 比如抓住时间守护者？- 糟糕的主意
- Like catching the Time Keeper? - Bad idea.
我们比谁先抓住时间守护者
First person to get the bad guy wins.
别再比赛了…
No. Not another competi…
我不是让你们淡定吗
What part of "chillax" don't you understand?
比就比
Game on.
真是的
Aw, man!
这个电击口香糖也不管用
This Electric Shock Gumball doesn't work, either.
你嚼口香糖的时候我却在研究我的锤子手
While you're chewing gum over there, I'm hacking into my Hammer Hands.
好像成了
I think I got it!
啊
Ow!
为什么
Why?
我真不明白
I just don't understand.
上面写着内含电池
It says batteries are included.
念念小字
Read the fine print.
里面不含有
"on and off button…
开关
…not included."
我们走吧
Let's get out of here.
好主意
Good idea.
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey! - Hey!
你们干什么你们没有资格到这里来
What are you kids doing? You don't have security clearance to be out here.
我们的狗走丢了
Um… We lost our dog.
但我们刚刚找到了它看
Yeah, but we just found him. See?
你们好 不对 汪汪 不对 嗷嗷
Hello. I mean, bark. I mean, woof, woof.
- 不应该是… - 别说了
- Definitely, I meant… - Shut up.
他们也不信看来我们要一起行动了
Yeah, they're not falling for it. Looks we're all in this together now.
快跑啊
Run!
- 嘿 - 喂 不要跑
- Hey! - Hey! Stop right there!
借过让一下你的鞋很漂亮
Oh, excuse me. Coming through. Nice shoes.
- 啊 - 对不起 对不起
- Oh! - Sorry, sorry.
拦住两个孩子
Stop those kids!
我们跑不过他们
We'll never outrun them!
会的拉我的项圈
Yes, we will! Pull my collar!
来一层油
Oil slick.
好棒啊
Awesome!
喔
Uh-oh.
- 还在追我们 - 拉我的尾巴
- They're still after us! - Pull my tail.
尾部投弹
Butt bombs.
这是史上最酷的狗
This is the coolest dog ever!
没错这是奖励我接受
Absolutely. That's an award and I accept it.
哇
Whoa!
等等还有一件事
Wait, wait, one more. one more.
拉我的手指
Pull my finger.
来啊
Do it.
等着
Wait for it.
这有什么用处
What was that supposed to do?
只为了让我笑笑
It just makes me laugh.
无声的致命武器
Silent but lethal.
我们怎么找到时间守护者
How are we gonna find the Time Keeper?
不知道肯定要比逃出休息室困难得多
I don't know, if it was that hard just getting out of the lounge.
这是远程传送电波发射器
This is the Telematic organism oscillation Transporter…
简称T00T
…otherwise known as TOOT.
卡门说过不要依赖于器械要开动大脑
Carmen said not to rely on our gadgets, but to use our heads.
阿格诺你对时间守护者了解多少
Argonaut, what do you know about the Time Keeper?
先输入我的密码
First, type in my passcode.
00汪
Double-O-Woof.
已经拦截了加密信息
They've intercepted several coded messages.
含有时间守护者的地点
as to the Time Keeper's location.
但没人能破解电码
But no one's been able to crack the code.
这不是密码是打乱了顺序
It's not a code. It's an anagram.
去掉所有数字
Drop all the numbers,
用剩下的字母组合成词
switch all the letters around, and it spells something else.
一流手表修理店？
"Big Time Watch Repair Shop"?
坏人在一家手表店威胁世界？
The bad guy is holding the world hostage from a watch shop?
他自称是时间守护者
Well, he is called the Time Keeper.
坏人确实希望他们的密室有个主题
Villains do love their secret hideouts to have a theme.
这能让我们不离开大楼
This will take us to the Time Keeper's shop.
就能把我们带到时间守护者的店
without having to leave the building.
最好别让我们四分五裂
You better not disintegrate us.
- 我觉得必须分裂才行 - 什么
- I think that's sort of the point. - What?
他们拿走了时间宝石别让他们跑了
They took the Chronos Sapphire. Don't let them get away!
你这家伙把我们汽化了
You weirdo! You vaporized us!
我的脸没了
I've lost face.
这里臭哄哄的
Something stinks around here.
我就知道你是个“屁股头”
I always knew you were a butthead.
我真想给你一拳只可惜找不到拳头
I'd give you a knuckle sandwich if I knew where my knuckles were!
我的胃里翻腾的厉害
Oh, I think my stomach is inside out.
我好像少了一个肾
I think I'm missing a kidney.
阿格诺
Argonaut!
骗了你们了
Got ya!
逗你玩呢
I'm just pulling your leg.
- 厉害 - 真搞笑
- Brilliant. - A comedian.
- 玛丽萨在电话上 - 玛丽萨
- Marissa's on the line. - Marissa?
好了孩子
OK, sweetheart.
- 喂 - 把通讯器给妈妈
- Hello? - Give Mommy the comlink.
好谢谢
There we go. Thank you.
对不起除了技术故障卡门孩子们怎么样
Sorry, technical difficulties, Carmen. How are the kids?
他们…
They're, uh…
在小睡
…napping?
好他们到底在哪儿
OK. Where are they really?
对不起他们把自己传送出了航天局
I'm really sorry. They TOOTed themselves out of the OSS.
把坐标发给我我们到那里见面
Send me their coordinates. I'll meet you there.
她很像你卡门
You know, she's a lot like you, Carmen.
这正是我担心的
That's what I'm afraid of.
你确定是这个地方吗
Are you sure this is the place?
我们想想他叫时间守护者
Let's think. He's called the Time Keeper.
这个房间都是钟表
This is a room full of clocks.
走我们去看看对面的奶酪店
Nah, let's go, let's check out that cheese shop across the road.
又是一个打乱顺序的词
It's another anagram.
还可以拼写成什么单词
Switch all those letters around and what do they spell?
爱茶的人
Oh, um, tea lover.
- 厉害 - 电梯
- Brilliant. - Elevator.
这肯定是入口
This must be the access panel.
- 哦 - 我赢了一次
- Oops. - One point for me.
也许是这个
Maybe this little guy.
我赢了两次
Two points for me.
- 你可以帮忙 - 冒着失败的风险？
- You could help, genius. - And risk losing?
密码正确
Password accepted.
你先别说赢了先看看通往哪里
Let's see where this leads before we call you the winner.
你们应该比赛谁更烦人
You should have a competition to see which one of you is the most annoying.
没用替身没用替身
All my own stunts, all my own stunts.
这是个巨大的钟表
And it's… a giant clock.
不这是个巨大的死亡陷阱
No, it's a giant death trap.
这是时针
That's the hour hand.
这是分针
The minute hand.
这是秒针
And that's the second hand.
那么
So, what's…
这是什么
…that?
这应该是切人的指针
That's probably the cut-you-in-half hand.
- 我要回家 - 那里有个门
- Well, I'm going home. - There's a door over there!
那又怎样
So?
第一个完整无缺跑过去的人
First person to get across without getting smushed…
获胜
…wins.
听我说看见别人跳悬崖
Now, listen, just because one person jumps off a cliff,
不要跟着跳下去是不是
it doesn't mean you have to follow them. Does it?
看来不是
Oh, it does, apparently.
好的我来了
Brilliant. Here we go again.
切人的指针来了
Here comes the cut-you-in-half hand!
- 跳 - 我还是趴下吧
- Jump! - I'll duck, thank you very much.
哇
Whoa!
肯定有更好的办法过去
There's gotta be a better way to pass the time.
又来了速度更快了
Here it comes again! It's moving faster!
因为时间加速了
That's because time is speeding up!
听着我的任务是看着你们不是看着你们去死
Listen, I was told to watch you kids, but not watch you die!
塞西尔坚持住
Cecil! Hang on!
这个看着好玩
Now this is fun to watch.
- 你怎么样 - 没事
- You OK? - Yeah.
我赢了一分
I win. one point for me.
- 哦 - 快来这里来
- Ow. - Come on. This way.
喂 起作用了
Hey… Hey, it's working!
漂亮
Sweet.
我搜寻间谍
I spy a spy.
去拿摄像机
Go get the camera.
表演时间
It's show time.
我的五年计划要实现了
My five-year plan is coming together.
这是我的重大突破
This is my big break.
在这次成功的基础上将来再实现黄金时间
Now we just build on this success and maybe someday hit primetime.
黄金时间就是自由时间陪着和孩子们
Primetime means free time… to spend with my kids.
好计划只不过五年以后就没有孩子了
Great plan. only in five years, they won't be kids anymore.
你说什么
What are you saying?
现在就抽出时间陪孩子
Spend the time now.
有件事你将来总会有时间
'Cause the one thing you'll always find time for later…
就是后悔
…is regret.
天
Jeez.
我们差点被切成两半就为了这台电脑？
We almost got cut in half for a computer?
上面有很多…
There's a lot here about…
“困在时间中的男孩”
"The Boy Trapped In Time."
如果不阻止时间守护者我们也将会这样
And that's gonna happen to us if we don't stop the Time Keeper.
根据电脑所说他曾经是时光旅行专家
According to this, he was part of a time travel experiment.
上世纪三十年代就有时光旅行？
Time travel in the 1930s?
那时的人有很多奇思异想
People sure did talk funny back then.
1936年决战计划录像
"Project Armageddon Test Footage, 1936.
时间宝石被发现是唯一能
Chronos Sapphire, discovered to be the only known element.
阻止决战装置的东西
able to stop the Armageddon device."
- 我们必须离开这里 - 怎么了
- We have to get out of here! - What's wrong?
他们在找这串项链
They're after the necklace!
这会停止你的表
That'll stop your clock.
小心碰头
Watch your head!
对不起
oops! Sorry about that.
但好消息是你的身高可以坐这趟车了
Well, the good news is, you're tall enough to go on all the rides.
玩间谍游戏？
Playing spy games?
你们孩子以为自己有无穷的时间
You children think you have all the time in the world,
但很快我就会有
but soon I will.
把项链交过来
Hand over the necklace.
我觉得你们应该找个更秘密的巢穴
I think it's time you found a more secret lair.
- 玛丽萨 - 什么
- Marissa! - What?
别碰我的孩子
Leave my kids alone.
继子
Stepkids.
嘘她是来救我们的
Shh! She's here to save us.
你们怎么能把时间浪费在这种争吵上
How dare you waste time bickering about that?
如果你们对于做家人没有兴趣
If you have no interest in being a family,
那就不配得到任何时间
then you don't deserve any time together.
他有一点说对了
Well, he's right about one thing.
我们要想离开这里的话就要像家人一样合作
If we're gonna get outta here, we need to work as a family.
启动你们的器械
Fire up your gadgets.
没有被启动
They're not activated.
- 只是纪念品 - 现在不是了
- They're just souvenirs. - Not anymore.
锤子时间
Hammer time.
酷
Cool.
一家钟表店？
A watch shop?
稍微向左继续绕着房子走
Slight left and proceed around building.
现在右拐
Turn right now.
发现间谍
Spy detected.
- 这是垃圾箱 - 发现间谍
- It's a dumpster. - Spy detected.
向前走左拐
Walk forward now. Turn left now.
左脚右脚左脚右脚一大步
Left foot, right foot, left foot, big right foot.
到中心停止
Center and stop.
向下继续
Proceed below.
这烦人的声音说这里有个间谍看
The annoying voice is saying there's a spy right here. Look.
现在向下
Proceed below now.
这不只是垃圾箱
This is more than a dumpster!
- 对不起 - 没关系 再来
- Sorry! - It's OK! Do it again!
天这么多香菇
Oh, shiitake mushrooms.
过来过来
Come here. Come here, come here.
准备
OK, ready?
我是间谍猎手威尔伯
Wilbur Wilson, Spy Hunter here.
你们看到我正在一处地下巢穴
As you can see, I'm in some sort of underground secret lair.
我们国家的顶级间谍
where the battle for freedom and justice.
正在为自由和正义而战
is being fought by our country's top spies.
在上面看不见很多
I really can't see much from up here.
但是经过放大就能看得清了
but we can zoom in with our Spy Hunt Cam and get a closer look.
我的孩子们看到以后会很激动的
Oh, the kids are gonna flip when they see this.
拍到了吗我们该走了
Did you get that? You got it? Go, go, go.
阿格诺别愣着了
Argonaut, do something!
我能干什么我是宠物不是战士
What do you want me to do? I'm a lover, not a fighter.
攻击模式
Attack mode!
攻击模式启动
Attack mode activated.
表演时间
It's show time!
加油阿格诺加油
Go, Argo, go!
谁把这段视频发到网上
Oh, someone put that on YouTube!
时间苍蝇陪你们玩玩
Time flies when you're having fun.
我的项链
My necklace!
我们带孩子离开这里
Let's get the kids out of here!
阿格诺
Argonaut!
放开
Release!
拜托我正打算把他埋在后院
Oh, come on! I was gonna bury him in the backyard!
让他们走这都是计划的一部分
Let them go. It's all part of the plan.
我们有了时间宝石
We have the Chronos Sapphire.
现在没什么能阻止我们了
Nothing can stop us now.
对不起丢失了项链玛丽萨
Sorry about the necklace, Marissa.
"Sorry about the necklace, Marissa."
当初就该还给你的
I should've given it back to you when you asked.
确实
Yes, you should've.
我们不知道时间守护者在找它
We had no idea the Time Keeper wanted it.
我们只是傻孩子
"We're just dumb kids."
你们不可能知道这是保密信息
You couldn't have known. It was classified.
世界有大麻烦了
The whole world's in big trouble.
别看我
Don't look at me.
都怪我们
It's all our fault.
对不起没告诉你们我是间谍
And I'm sorry I didn't share with you that I was a spy.
但重要的是你们安全
But it was important to me that you were both protected and safe.
重要的是阻止时间守护者
What's important is stopping the Time Keeper.
再给我们一次机会
Give us another chance.
你两个这么勇敢我很自豪
You two have been so very brave and I'm so proud of you.
这像是我妈妈会说的话
That sounds like something my mom would say.
- 总部让我们回去汇报 - 带孩子回到航天局
- They want us back for a debrief. - Take the kids back to OSS.
- 我随后就到 - 好的
- I'll meet you there. - Got it.
谢谢你救了我们
Thanks for rescuing us.
不客气
Any time.
我以前经常这么惹麻烦
I used to get in trouble like this all the time.
嗨老婆对不起没给你打通有好消息
Hi, sweetheart. Sorry I missed you. Great news!
我拍下了一个真正的间谍在钟表店里的打斗
I got the most amazing footage of a real spy battle at the watch shop!
我将在今晚黄金时间播出
I'm gonna put it on the air tonight, primetime!
- 你和孩子们会很自豪的 - 哦 不
- The kids are gonna be so proud. - Oh, no.
爱你想你需要你再见给我回电话
Love you, miss you, need you. Bye! Call me back!
你成功了间谍猎手
You did it, Spy Hunter.
这太棒了
That's great!
我们将凭此获得艾米奖普利策奖
We're gonna win an Emmy for this. A Pulitzer.
后退后退她还带着个宝宝？
Whoa, go back, go back. Does she have a baby with her?
是的真是无价之宝
Oh, she does! Oh, that's priceless!
我们要打上字幕：间谍是不称职的母亲
OK, we're gonna need a graphic that reads "Spies Are Unfit Moms."
威尔伯你再问问儿童保护机构的看法
And, Wilbur, see if you can get a quote from Child Protective Services.
运气好的话他们会把宝宝带走送到寄养家庭
If we're lucky, they'll take the kids away, put 'em in foster care! Yeah!
- 威尔伯 - 对不起我笨手笨脚的
- Wilbur! - Sorry. I'm a klutz.
没关系这里还有原来的胶片
It's all right. I've got the original tape right here.
忘了吃午饭了
Hm! Didn't get any lunch.
味道就像鸡肉你们吃吗
Tastes like chicken! Want some?
出去
out!
天
Jeez.
发现间谍
Spy detected.
是吗很好
Oh, really? Great.
嗨亲爱的
Hi, honey.
别叫我亲爱的已经没什么亲爱了
Don't "honey" me. There's no "honey"ing anymore.
你是间谍
You're a spy!
- 你发现了 - 我是间谍猎手嘛
- You found out. - Well, I'm a Spy Hunter.
看来我水平不行因为和一个间谍生活在一起
And apparently I'm not a very good one, since I've been living with one.
我临产那天就辞职了
I retired the day we had the baby…
因为家人对我来说是最重要的
…because our family is the most important thing in the world to me.
另外…
And…
真对不起
…I'm so sorry.
我感觉自己像傻瓜
Wow. I feel like such a fool.
你为何嫁给我
Why did you marry me?
- 是跟人打赌输了吧 - 你是我爱的人
- You must've lost a bet, right? - You're the man I love.
而现在我是失业的人
Well, uh, now I'm the man without a job.
或许也要失去家庭
and maybe without a family.
孩子们呢
Where are the kids?
他们正在航天局的保护之下
They're under protective surveillance at the OSS.
可能在那里更安全
They're probably safer there anyway.
他们的亲生父亲没本事保护
I mean, their own dad can't protect them.
告诉他们我爱他们
Just tell them I love them.
可我们呢
What about us?
我只是…
I just…
需要一点时间
…need time.
我们的时间都不多了
We're all running out of time.
有人预测世界末日将是一团大火
Some predicted it would come in a blaze of fire,
一次大洪水但只有古代玛雅人说对了
a giant flood, but it was the ancient Mayans who got it right.
他们预测是人类日历的终结
when they predicted an end to the human calendar,
时间的终点
the end of time itself.
谁能拯救我们避免迫在眉睫的毁灭？
Can anyone save us from this impending apocalypse,
这次最终的末日这次…
this final doomsday, this…
末日
Armageddon.
也称为威尔斯实验
Also known as the Wells Experiment.
在当时这个奇妙的装置
Back in the day, this contraption.
差点导致我们世界的终结
almost caused the end of the world as we know it.
所以航天局终止了这次试验
That's why the OSS shut the experiment down.
把这装置至于1 3级安全防范中直到今天
and placed the device in Level 13 lockdown, where it remains today.
世界的命运系于一发
The fate of the world is on the line here.
所以我召来了我们最出色的特工之一
That's why I'm calling upon one of our most valued and skilled operatives,
考特特工
Agent Cortez.
他本已退役却毅然来帮助我们
He has even come out of retirement to help us.
耶
Yeah!
弟弟
Oh, brother.
- 很高兴回来 - 当初就不该走的
- It's good to be back. - Then you never should have left.
你这7年去了哪里？
Where have you been the last seven years?
告诉你了还算是秘密任务吗
If I told you, then it wouldn't be called a secret mission.
我也不稀罕知道我只庆幸能摆脱你
It's not like I missed you or anything. I needed a break from your face.
真是巧了
Oh, what an incredible coincidence.
- 我也庆幸能摆脱你 - 随你吧
- I needed a break from yours. - Oh, whatever.
他们怎么回事
What's going on over there?
家人重逢
Family reunion.
- 我们的事不重要 - 天啊
- This isn't about us. - Gosh.
卡门重要的是拯救世界
Carmen, this is about saving the world.
- 你不配这个徽章 - 啊
- You don't deserve to wear this badge. - Uh…
- 谢谢 - 不客气
- Thanks. - You're welcome.
好了特工们让我们确保还有明天
All right, agents. Let's make sure there is a tomorrow.
我们去拯救世界吧
Let's go save the world!
我们做什么我们的任务呢
What do we get to do? What's our assignment?
你输了
You lose!
真是的为什么让我们休息
Man! Why are we in time-out?
是我们找到了时间守护者为什么不让我们去
We found the Time Keeper. So, why are we grounded?
为什么让我们看孩子
And why do we have to watch the baby?
严格来说是我看着她？
Technically, I'm watching her.
有时我是一条狗有时是儿童娱乐中心
Sometimes you're the dog, sometimes you're the baby entertainment center.
我是邓杰航天局主任
Danger D'Amo, director of the OSS.
我想赞扬你们勇敢的贡献
I wanted to commend you on your brave service.
你们的才能很随你们妈妈
You bobbleheads really take after your mom.
后妈
Stepmom.
我给你个建议孩子
Let me give you some advice, kiddo.
不要受这种想法的影响
Don't get balled up over that kind of baloney.
她花时间爱你你也要爱她
She takes the time to love you… you love her back.
- 漂亮的手表 - 谢谢
- Nice watch. - Thanks.
是我老爸送我的
It was a gift from my pops.
- 你说话很有趣 - 你长得很有趣
- You sure talk funny. - You sure look funny.
- 邓杰·迪亚摩 - 对
- Danger D'Amo. - Yeah.
知道你的名字是打乱顺序的词吗
Did you know your name is an anagram?
把你的名字中的字母打乱一下顺序就是…
Switch the letters of your name around, and it spells…
末日
…Armageddon.
末日装置的末日
As in the Armageddon device.
这要么是巧合
Either that's a coincidence…
要么只是偶然的巧合
…or that's just an incredible coincidence.
你在滴答响
You're ticking.
这是老表
It's an old watch.
可你戴着三只表
But you're wearing three more.
你就是时间守护者
You're the Time Keeper.
我很想和你们聊聊但是时间不多了
Yeah. I'd love to stick around and chat but time is running out.
好人中的老大就是坏人中的老大？
The head of the good guys is actually the head of the bad guys?
我倒没料到
I did not see that coming.
我们被困在这里了
We're trapped in here!
找个通讯器或者电话
Look around for a comlink or a phone!
我们必须通知玛丽萨
We have to warn Marissa!
我是威尔森特工
Agent Wilson.
- 转身 - 这是陷阱
- Turn around! - It's a trap!
- 时间守护者就是邓杰 - 这是他的真实身份
- Time Keeper is Danger! - That's his secret identity!
我没时间陪你们玩
Look, I don't have time for your pranks right now. OK?
跟阿格诺学着看孩子谢谢
Watch Argonaut watch the baby. Thank you.
末日装置
The Armageddon device.
这么小
It's tiny.
如果时间是个测试家人是最合适的
If time's the test, family is best.
这是陷阱
It's a trap.
你们好特工你们来得很准时
Hello, agents. You're right on time.
孩子们是对的
The kids were right.
看来我不是
I guess I'm not…
你们以为的那个人
…who you thought I was.
那么真正的末日装置在哪儿
So where's the real Armageddon device?
在航天局一直在那里
Back at the OSS, where it's always been.
现在
And now…
我要回去了
…I must get back to it.
这是什么
What's that?
一只好表
A really nice watch.
也是航天局所有特工的
It's also a freeze transmitter.
冷冻发射器
for all agents at the OSS.
该去掉我的对手了
It's time to take out the competition.
邓杰不要
Danger, don't.
现在停止世界
Now… to stop the world.
我怎么没冷冻
Why didn't I freeze?
我被困在这里了
I'm… trapped in here.
我需要增援
I need reinforcements.
但是没有后援都被定住了
But there are no reinforcements. They're all frozen.
不过
Except…
世界上大多地方的时间都耗尽了
Time has run out for most of the planet.
十八个时区的时间
Eighteen time zones have been frozen.
已经被时间守护者的末日装置停止
by the Time Keeper's Armageddon device.
可以确定的是正朝我们而来
One thing's for certain… it's heading our way.
但是我们不能放弃希望
But we must not lose hope.
坑爹呢？没希望了我们死定了
Who are we kidding? It's over! We're toast!
请注意特工小子你们已经被征召
Attention, Spy Kids. You have been activated.
重复你们已经被征召
I repeat, you have been activated.
他和我们说话？
Is he talking to us?
现在时间守护者正要占据航天局总部
At this very moment, the Time Keeper is taking over OSS Headquarters.
你们拯救世界的时刻到了
Your time has come to save the world.
全部航天局特工都被定住
Every OSS agent has been frozen.
要靠你们去关闭末日装置
It's up to you to shut down the Armageddon device.
抢回项链这是唯一能阻止它的东西
Get the necklace back. It's the only thing that can stop him.
我们怎么能抢回来
And how are we supposed to do that?
特工小子总是能打败坏人
Spy Kids have always been able to beat the bad guys.
因为大人太多虑了
because adults over-think things.
但对孩子来说一切都是可能的
But to a kid, everything is possible.
相信我我知道
Trust me, I know.
只要用你们的想象力合作
Just use your imagination and work with each other,
而不是对抗
not against each other.
那么不再比赛了
So no more competing against each other?
好的
Good.
- 阿格诺 - 攻击模式帮帮忙
- Argonaut! - Attack mode, por favor.
- 撞开门 - 小菜一碟
- Attack the door. - Argo smash!
宝宝怎么办
What about the baby?
特工小子
Spy Kids.
特工狗
Spy Dog.
特工宝宝
Spy Baby.
既然你们现在成了特工小子
Now that you've been activated as Spy Kids,
就是精英部队的一员了
you are part of an elite team,
我们要合作就像朱尼所说
and we need to work together, like Juni said.
不能再竞争
No more competitions.
我们要闯进航天局密室
We've got to break into the OSS vault,
找到时间守护者
get to the Time Keeper,
找到时间宝石
find the Chronos Sapphire,
然后用它来阻止末日装置
then use it to stop the Armageddon device,
当然也拯救世界
and, of course, save the world.
塞西尔你负责密室丽贝卡你负责恶作剧
Cecil, you take the vault. Rebecca, you're on pranks.
至于我当然是最艰巨的任务
And l, of course, will take the toughest assignment of all…
看孩子
I'll watch the baby.
原来他定住特工
So I realized the only way he could freeze agents.
就是通过航天局的徽章
was through their OSS badges.
好了
There you go.
谢谢你扔掉我的徽章 卡门
Thanks for trashing mine, Carmen.
谢谢朱尼 解开你姐姐
Thanks, Juni. Unfreeze your sister.
好的但首先
OK, but first…
我要留个纪念
…this is how I remember you.
好了
And there we go.
- 朱尼 - 嗯？
- Juni! - Hm?
解开她
Unfreeze her.
可是这样多安静啊
But it's so peaceful and quiet.
好了
There.
如果是我带领行动就不会发生这种事
This never would've happened if I was mission leader.
- 我征召了丽贝卡和塞西尔 - 什么
- I activated Rebecca and Cecil. - What?
你低估他们的能力了
They're more ready than you think.
如果他们有个三长两短你就死定了
If anything happens to those kids, you're toast.
这里来
This way.
你真行啊
Real smooth, diaper lady.
我只是根据直觉
I was just following my instincts.
你的直觉烂透了
Well, your in-stinks!
你们本是最棒的间谍组合
You two were the best spy team ever.
怎么变成这样
What happened?
是啊你这么多年去哪儿了
Yeah. Where have you been all these years?
我想靠自己闯荡也努力了
I tried to strike out on my own, and I struck out. OK?
父母把家族的生意也留给你一半
OK, but Mom and Dad left the family business to the both of us.
是的不过
Yeah. Well…
我觉得继续和我姐姐一起工作很没出息
I guess I thought it wasn't cool to keep working with my sister.
这样才有出息
It's what would've made you cool.
玛丽萨呢
Where's Marissa?
这是沼泽
It's quicksand!
别逼我把你打晕
Don't make me punch your lights out.
他在那里
Hey, there he is!
你们见识我黑暗的一面了
Now you've seen my dark side.
电量不足
Low battery?
不要依赖于器械
"Don't rely on your gadgets."
嗯
Hmm…
喂
Hello?
有人吗
Is anyone in here?
你打开门了吗
You get the door open yet?
我们需要走别的路
I think we need another way in.
好我一会就到
OK. I'll be there in a minute.
恭喜
Congratulations.
你抓住了一个孩子
You caught a kid.
一路顺风
Enjoy the ride!
现在怎么办
Now what?
我们投降
We give up.
这是拿回项链的唯一办法
It's the only way we'll get the necklace back.
听我的暗示
Just follow my lead.
交出武器
Hand over your weapons.
全部武器
All of your weapons.
航天局特工都被时间定住了
OSS agents have been frozen in time.
还有人能拯救吗
Is there someone, anyone, out there that can save the day?
你好威尔伯
Hello, Wilbur.
是的我是你的狗我在说话但是现在别管这个了
Yes, this is your dog, and I'm talking, but never mind about that now.
丽贝卡和塞西尔有了危险
Rebecca and Cecil are in danger.
被时间守护者抓住了需要你的帮助
They've been captured by the Time Keeper and they need your help.
这话你可能不信不过你是他们最后的希望
I know it's hard to believe, sir, but you're their last hope.
我劝你快点
I'd hurry if I were you.
你们在比划什么呢
What's with the jazz hands? Huh, kiddies?
我弟弟有听力障碍而你这个笨蛋手下拿走了他的助听器
My brother's hearing impaired. And your goon took his hearing aids.
把助听器还给他 我们不是恶人
Give him his hearing aids back. We're not monsters here.
确实不是你只是要终结世界而已
No. You're only trying to end the world.
你为何要这么做
Why are you doing this?
末日装置不是为了结束世界或停止时间
The Armageddon device was not meant to end the world or stop time.
是为了让时间倒流
It was meant to travel back in time.
让我回到这个时候
To get me back to that.
- 我的父亲 - 儿子过来看看
- My father. - Son, come here! Take a look at this.
威尔斯实验是进行时间旅行的早期尝试
The Wells Experiment was an early attempt to time travel.
这是出事之前的我
That's me before the accident.
我父亲正在研究机器原型
My father was working on the original prototype.
正准备开始测试机器却出了意外
They were just about to test the machine when it went haywire.
他让我不要靠近实验室
He told me not to play near the lab.
可我从来不听
But I never listened.
我被困在时间中很多年
It trapped me in time for so many years I almost lost count.
你就是被定在时间中的男孩
You were the Boy Frozen In Time.
我父亲用一生的时间
My father spent his entire life…
想拯救我
…trying to set me free.
我看着他变老
I watched him grow old…
以及最后的
…and, eventually…
去世
…die.
航天局终止了试验
The OSS shut down the experiment.
用了一个天外来的物质
with a solution that literally fell from the sky…
时间宝石
… the Chronos Sapphire.
等效果消失以后我成了孩子身体的成年人
When the effects wore off, I was a grown man in a boy's body.
我的朋友都去世了
All my friends were gone.
我父亲
My father…
去世了
…gone.
我所爱的一切都不在了
Everything and everyone I cared about was no more.
那你这么做只是为了再看你父亲一眼？
And all of this is so you can see your father again?
我希望有更多的时间
I want more time!
和他在一起
With him.
他给了我一切
He gave me everything.
我却忽视了他
And I couldn't even give him the time of day,
因为我当时不知道
because I didn't know…
我们在一起的时间有这么短
…that our time would be so short together.
但是等我回去就不一样了
But now when I go back, things are gonna be different.
- 不可能 - 你说什么
- No, they won't. - Excuse me?
你不可能回到从前
You can't actually travel through time.
时间是不变的
Time stays the same.
你只能是创造出
You're just creating multiple versions of yourself.
出现在不同时间的自己
that appear at different points in time.
他错了我们的计划会奏效的
He's wrong. our plan will work.
你以前试过也失败了
You've tried this before and failed.
据我估计你们
And my guess is that you've…
已经多次回到从前
…already gone back in time a lot.
这不是你第一次回到从前
This isn't the first time you've traveled back.
你每次回来就会变得更糟
And every time you return, you come back worse.
每一次你的计划都失败了
Each time, your plan fails.
你用另一个自己再次尝试
You try it again with another you.
可你什么时候才能明白
But when are you going to learn…
你无法改变过去？
…you can't change the past?
你只会导致世界末日
You will only cause Armageddon.
别听他的这一次会奏效的
Don't listen to him. This time, it will work!
你能回去然后你就有无穷无尽的时间
You will go back and you will have all the time in the world.
和你父亲在一起
to spend with your father.
邓杰我母亲去世的时候
Danger, when my mom died,
是我最痛苦的时候
it was the worst thing that could ever happen to me.
我也希望能有更多时间和她在一起
I wished I had more time with her.
没有回头路
There is no going back.
珍惜你和他在一起的时间
Honor the years you had with him.
那些简短的
Those brief…
特殊的时刻
…special moments…
是我们会永远记住的
…are the ones we'll remember.
关键不在于你有多少时间
It's not about how much time you have.
而在于你如何利用这些时间
It's what you choose to do with it.
末日倒计时20分钟
T minus 20 minutes until Armageddon.
时间漩涡打开了
The Time Vortex is opening!
你们怎么逃出我的沙漏的？
How'd you get outta my sand trap?
凭着赤手空拳
With my bare hands.
其实是用我的自动唇膏
Actually, it was my Atomic Lipstick.
别碰我的继子
Keep away from my stepkids.
应该说是你的孩子
Make that your kids.
好的
All right.
应该说是特工小子
Make that your Spy Kids.
别碰我的特工小子
Stay away from my Spy Kids.
来不及了
Too late!
奏效了奏效了
It worked! It worked!
除了我们世界上的人都在固定中
Everyone in the world is frozen except us.
还有我们
And us.
时间宝石
The Chronos!
别放开手表否则就会被定住
Don't let go of the watch or you'll freeze!
我们必须用项链
We have to use the necklace.
来永远停止末日装置
to stop the Armageddon device once and for all!
进入漩涡
Get into the Vortex.
等等你没有锤子手
Wait, you don't have your Hammer Hands.
不需要锤子手
I don't need Hammer Hands.
- 耶 - 塞西尔
- Yeah! - Cecil!
喂是玛丽萨送给我的
Hey, Marissa gave that to me!
- 别这么做邓杰 - 你无法找回过去
- Don't do it, Danger! - You can't bring back the past!
时间是青春的敌人
Time is the enemy of youth.
我要找回我的青春
I'm getting mine back.
你不会改变任何事
You won't change anything!
你不是说不会改变任何事吗
I thought you said nothing would change.
等着看吧
Wait for it.
这是谁
Who's that?
这是邓杰
That's Danger.
你们说的对
You were right.
无法回到从前
You can't go back.
我试过了
I tried.
我的父亲仍然死了
My father still died…
不管我如何去救他
…no matter what I tried to do to save him.
他告诉我一句话
He did tell me one thing.
很重要的一句话
that was very important.
要好好生活
You have to live life.
向前看不是向后
moving forwards, not back.
这一次
This time…
我会听他的
…I'm gonna listen to him.
孩子们
Kids!
玛丽萨
Marissa!
我很担心你们你们怎么样
I was so worried about you guys. Are you OK?
- 没事 - 很抱歉把你们牵涉进来
- Yeah. - I'm so sorry I brought you into this.
史上最差的继母
Worst stepmom ever.
是啊
Yeah.
不过是史上最棒的间谍妈妈我喜欢你本来的样子
But best spy mom ever! I like when you're being yourself.
来
Come here.
你们以为阻止我了？
You think you've stopped me?
你们什么也没有阻止
You've stopped nothing.
我们会一遍遍的干下去
We're just gonna keep doing this over and over and over again.
直到我得到我想要的
until I get what I want!
因为这一次时间在我一边
Because this time, time is on my side!
是的在监狱的时间
Yeah. Hard time.
- 打倒你们了 - 哇
- Clocked ya. - Whoa!
你蒙的
Lucky punch!
你怎么找到我们的
How'd you find us?
我是威尔伯你们的爸爸
I'm Wilbur Wilson, your father.
你是最酷的爸爸
You're the coolest dad ever.
我不会等着将来有足够的时间陪你们
I'm not gonna wait until I have enough time for us to spend together.
从今以后
From now on…
我会挤出时间
…we're gonna make time.
这才是英雄气概
Now that's heroic.
那么
So…
你是间谍？
You're a spy?
是的我是间谍
Yeah. I'm a spy.
那么
Well…
我是间谍猎手
…I'm a Spy Hunter.
抓住你了
Got you.
永远不会放你走
And I'm never letting go.
这就是家庭时光
Now this is family time.
我和朱尼决定做
Juni and I have decided to become co-leaders.
新的特工小子计划的共同负责人
of the new Spy Kids program.
我们需要招兵买马
We're gonna need some new recruits.
心灵手巧有创造力机智的孩子
with ingenuity, creativity, and heads-up thinking.
丽贝卡 塞西尔
Rebecca, Cecil?
当然还有…
And of course…
间谍宝宝
…Spy Baby.
宝宝要给你们一个惊喜
Yeah. Baby's got a surprise for you.
别…这是…
Don't get… This is it, group, that's it. Just…
宝宝会走路了
Baby's first steps!
孩子走路有什么稀奇狗说话才稀奇呢
You're more impressed by a kid standing up than a dog that can talk?
等一下
Hold on a second, l…
漂亮
Nice!
宝宝打倒的第一个坏人
Oh! Baby's first bad guy!
- 哇 - 是我教的
- Wow! - I taught her that.
这个
Well…
有志不在年高嘛
…you can never start 'em too young.
妈妈真为你骄傲
Mommy's so proud of you!
我们的时间又回来了回到我们的快乐时光
We are back on the clock, back to taking our own sweet time.
来笑来哭来拥抱我们所爱的人
to laugh, to cry, to embrace our loved ones.
我们有无穷无尽的时间
We have all the time in the world.
真的吗
or do we?
语音激活特工小子招募行动
Voice activate. Operation Spy Kid Recruitment.
寻找天才儿童
Identifying possible talent.
把过滤器调到最高
Setting filters to max.
你被征召了
You have been activated.
你也被征召了
And you have been activated.
我现在宣布你们是特工小子了
I now declare you all Spy Kids.
我赢了一分
That's one point for me.
唉哟
ouch.
欢呼
Cheers.